export const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "What does a yellow diamond-shaped sign with black symbols represent?",
    options: [
      "School zone ahead",
      "Stop sign ahead",
      "Yield to oncoming traffic",
      "Construction zone ahead",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "School zone ahead",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "When should you use your headlights in British Columbia?",
    options: [
      "30 minutes after sunset",
      "Only in heavy rain or fog",
      "30 minutes before sunrise",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What does a flashing red traffic light indicate?",
    options: [
      "Stop, proceed when safe",
      "Yield, proceed with caution",
      "Slow down, prepare to stop",
      "Merge into the next lane",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stop, proceed when safe",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "In a roundabout, which direction should you always travel?",
    options: [
      "Clockwise",
      "Counterclockwise",
      "Right turn only",
      "Left turn only",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Counterclockwise",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the speed limit in a residential area in British Columbia?",
    options: ["40 km/h", "50 km/h", "30 km/h", "60 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "50 km/h",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should you do when approaching a railway crossing with flashing lights?",
    options: [
      "Stop and wait for the lights to stop flashing",
      "Speed up to cross quickly",
      "Proceed with caution",
      "Honk your horn continuously",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stop and wait for the lights to stop flashing",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What does a solid yellow line on the road indicate?",
    options: [
      "No passing allowed",
      "Pass with caution",
      "Pass only on the right",
      "Pass only on the left",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "No passing allowed",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "When parking uphill with a curb, which way should your wheels be turned?",
    options: [
      "Towards the curb",
      "Away from the curb",
      "Parallel to the curb",
      "No specific direction",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Away from the curb",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the blood alcohol concentration (BAC) limit for drivers under 21 years old in BC?",
    options: ["0.08%", "0.04%", "0.02%", "Zero tolerance"],
    correctAnswer: "Zero tolerance",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "When can you proceed at a flashing yellow traffic signal?",
    options: [
      "After stopping and yielding",
      "Only during daylight hours",
      "When pedestrians are not present",
      "When it's safe to proceed",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "When it's safe to proceed",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should you do when encountering a school bus with flashing red lights?",
    options: [
      "Pass quickly",
      "Proceed with caution",
      "Stop until lights stop flashing",
      "Honk to alert the driver",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stop until lights stop flashing",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What does a white rectangular sign with black letters indicate?",
    options: [
      "Exit ahead",
      "Speed limit ahead",
      "Informational sign",
      "Hospital zone ahead",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Informational sign",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "When can you make a U-turn at an intersection?",
    options: [
      "Only at traffic lights",
      "When there's no oncoming traffic",
      "During rush hours",
      "Never at an intersection",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Never at an intersection",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should you do if your vehicle starts to skid on a slippery road?",
    options: [
      "Brake hard to stop",
      "Steer in the opposite direction of the skid",
      "Accelerate to gain control",
      "Hold the steering wheel straight",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Steer in the opposite direction of the skid",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What does a blue circle with a white arrow indicate?",
    options: [
      "One-way street",
      "Mandatory turn ahead",
      "Roundabout ahead",
      "Keep right",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Mandatory turn ahead",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What does a green traffic light mean?",
    options: ["Stop", "Proceed with caution", "Slow down", "Go"],
    correctAnswer: "Go",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "When can you pass on the right in British Columbia?",
    options: [
      "On one-way streets only",
      "When the vehicle ahead is making a left turn",
      "When the vehicle ahead is turning right",
      "Never on the right",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "When the vehicle ahead is making a left turn",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the maximum speed limit on a highway outside a municipality in British Columbia?",
    options: ["90 km/h", "100 km/h", "110 km/h", "120 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "120 km/h",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What should you do if you miss your exit on a freeway?",
    options: [
      "Reverse and go back",
      "Continue to the next exit",
      "Stop on the shoulder",
      "Make a U-turn at the next opportunity",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Continue to the next exit",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the penalty for distracted driving in British Columbia?",
    options: [
      "Verbal warning",
      "Fine and demerit points",
      "License suspension",
      "Community service",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Fine and demerit points",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of a HOV (High Occupancy Vehicle) lane?",
    options: [
      "Reserved for electric vehicles",
      "Express lane for emergency vehicles",
      "Carpool lane for vehicles with multiple occupants",
      "Exclusive lane for large trucks",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Carpool lane for vehicles with multiple occupants",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does a diamond-shaped sign with an orange background represent?",
    options: [
      "Railway crossing ahead",
      "Construction zone ahead",
      "School zone ahead",
      "Hospital zone ahead",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Construction zone ahead",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "When should you use your four-way flashers (hazard lights)?",
    options: [
      "During heavy rain",
      "When parking on the side of the road",
      "To alert other drivers of a problem",
      "When driving in a school zone",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To alert other drivers of a problem",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the recommended safe following distance in ideal driving conditions?",
    options: ["One car length", "Two seconds", "Five seconds", "Ten seconds"],
    correctAnswer: "Two seconds",
    userAnswer: "",
  },
];
